Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
- Series VI. Drawings and Plans
  - Filed Plans
    - Round Hill Golf Course, S. Dartmouth, MA (Box 185, Folder 24)
    - Rio Rico (Box 185, Folder 25)
    - Rivershore (Box 185, Folder 26)
    - Royal Lahaina (Box 185, Folder 27)
    - Sardinia (Box 185, Folder 28)
    - Sugarbush (Box 185, Folder 29)
    - Seabrook (Box 185, Folder 30)
    - Spyglass (Box 185, Folder 31)
    - Sea Island (Box 185, Folder 32)
    - Soto Grande (Box 185, Folder 33)
    - Sugar Creek (Box 185, Folder 34)
    - Stone Mountain (Box 185, Folder 35)
    - Spring Green (Box 185, Folder 36)
    - Sea Bright (Box 185, Folder 37)
    - St. Charles Country Club (Box 185, Folder 38)
    - St. Andrews Golf Club (Box 185, Folder 39)
    - Southern Woods (Box 185, Folder 40)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 185, Folder 41)
    - Siwanoy, New Rochelle NY (Box 185, Folder 42)
    - Old Warson country club (Box 185, Folder 43)
    - Oglebay (Box 185, Folder 44)
    - Oakland Hills (Box 185, Folder 45)
    - Onondaga (Box 185, Folder 46)
    - Myrtle Beach (Box 185, Folder 47)
    - Green sketches (Box 185, Folder 48)
    - Mauna Kea (Box 185, Folder 49)
    - Madaline Island (Box 185, Folder 50)
    - Georgia (Box 185, Folder 51)
    - Manzanilla (Box 185, Folder 52)
    - Mor (Box 185, Folder 53)
    - Upper Montclair Country Club (Box 185, Folder 54)
    - Metro West (Box 185, Folder 55)
    - Minn (Box 185, Folder 56)
    - Merion (Box 185, Folder 57)
    - Marine Park (Box 185, Folder 58)
    - Mantauk (Box 185, Folder 59)
    - Montclair (Box 185, Folder 60)
    - Miami (Box 185, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous sketches (Box 185, Folder 62)
    - Belle Meade (Box 185, Folder 63)
    - Clearwater (Box 185, Folder 64)
    - Detroit sketches (Box 185, Folder 65)
    - Fort Worth (Box 185, Folder 66)
    - Fairlawn NJ (Box 185, Folder 67)
    - Oakland Hills (Box 185, Folder 68)
    - Japan green sketches (Box 185, Folder 69)
    - Scona lodge (Box 185, Folder 70)
    - Yellowstone Country Club, MT (Box 185, Folder 71)
    - South Eleuthera Properties Limited, the Bay Companies, 1963-1966 (Box 201, Folder 1-3)
    - South Eleuthera Properties reports and notices, 1960-1961 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - South Eleuthera Properties correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Cotton Bay Club, 1960 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - South Eleuthera Properties meetings, 1959-1961 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Hammer, Colts Neck, 1978 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Papers for tax return [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Salerno, Pescia, 1961-1968 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - South Palm Canyon Project, 1967 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Essex Development, 1969 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Madeline Island, Wisconsin, 1965 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Salerno, Pescia prop, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Eleuthera taxes [RESTRICTED], 1960-1962 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Loan Inc., 1967 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Barclay's Bank, 1965-1967 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Current matters, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous notes and memos, 1962-1965 (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Geographic Tube list (old numbers) (Box 220)
    - Tube index cards (old numbers) (Box 218)
    - Acapulco (Box 227, Folder 22)
    - Aecola (Box 227, Folder 23)
    - Atlanta (Box 227, Folder 24)
    - Augusta (Box 227, Folder 25)
    - Augusta National (Box 227, Folder 26)
    - Bally Bumon (Box 227, Folder 27)
    - Bellerive Country Club (Box 227, Folder 28)
    - Bellport Village (Box 227, Folder 29)
    - Bellvue - Greens (Box 227, Folder 30)
    - Bercuit Greens (Box 227, Folder 31)
    - Birmingham (Box 227, Folder 32)
    - Biscayne (Box 227, Folder 33)
    - Blind Brook (Box 227, Folder 34)
    - Bloomfield Hills (Box 227, Folder 35)
    - Boyne (Box 227, Folder 36)
    - Broadmoor Golf Club, Colorado Springs, CO (Box 227, Folder 37)
    - Buffalo (Box 227, Folder 38)
    - Burlingame (Box 227, Folder 39)
    - Burning Tree Club, Bethesda, MD (Box 227, Folder 40)
    - Druid Hills Golf Course (Box 227, Folder 41)
    - Dar Es Salam (Box 227, Folder 42)
    - Dorado Beach (Box 227, Folder 43)
    - Unknown with "E" (Box 227, Folder 44)
    - Elkridge (Box 227, Folder 45)
    - Eugene Country Club, Eugene, OR (Box 227, Folder 46)
    - Gulph Mills (Box 227, Folder 47)
    - Muttontown Golf and Country Club (Box 227, Folder 48)
    - Oakland Hills (Box 227, Folder 49)
    - Old Lyme (Box 227, Folder 50)
    - Palmetto Dunes (Box 227, Folder 51)
    - Point Aquarius (Box 227, Folder 52)
    - Sea Bright (Box 227, Folder 53)
    - Tammy Brook (Box 227, Folder 54)
    - Tam O'Shanter Golf Course (Box 227, Folder 55)
    - Topsfield Inn and Country Club, Danvers, MA (Box 227, Folder 56)
    - Wilmington Country Club (Box 227, Folder 57)
    - Green Sketches - Current (Box 227, Folder 58)
    - Green Sketches (Box 227, Folder 59)
    - Unknown (1) (Box 227, Folder 60)
    - Unknown (2) (Box 227, Folder 61)
  - Rolled Plans
    - United States
      Alphabetical by State
      - Alabama
        - Aquarius Point, 431
        - Big Cove, 431
        - Birmingham - Birmingham, Country Club of, 86
        - Birmingham - Oxmoor Valley, 94, 95, 432
        - Calhoun, 87
        - Dothan, 88, 433
        - Florence - Turtle Point Yacht and Country Club, 98
        - Greenville, 89, 90
        - Huntsville, 90, 91, 432
        - Logan Martin Lake Project, 471
        - Mobile - Forest Lakes Country Club, 86
        - Mobile - Mobile Country Club, 86, 92, 93, 94, 431, 432
        - Opelika/Auburn, 96
        - Sunbelt, 96, 97, 98
      - Arizona
        - Litchfield Park - Wigwam Golf Course, 103
        - Phoenix - Arizona-Biltmore, 99
        - Rio Rico - Rio Rico Golf Course, 101
        - Tucson - Oracle Ranch, 100
        - The Pointe at Topatio Cliffs, 102
      - California
        - Apple Valley - Spring Valley Lake Golf Course, 125
        - Bayside - Bayside, 104
        - Beverly Hills - Beverly Hills Country Club, 105
        - Bodega Bay - Bodega Harbour, 107
        - Bonny Doon, 108
        - Burlingame - Burlingame Country Club, 109
        - El Caballero, 434
        - Calabasas - Calabasas Park Golf Course, 435
        - Carmel Valley - Green Meadows, Inc., 116
        - Carmelvaurt, 108
        - Coachella Valley, 110
        - Colton, 111
        - Concord - Concord Country Club, 111
        - Del Monte/Monterey Peninsula - Pebble Beach Golf Course, 121
        - Descauso - Boulder Oaks, 108
        - Fairfield - Rockville Hills, 121
        - Huntington Beach - Huntington Beach Property, 118
        - Los Angeles - Los Angeles Country Club, 110
        - Monterey - Laguna Seca Golf Ranch, 118
        - Monterey Peninsula, 119, 121
        - Monticello, 119
        - Murrieta - Murrieta Hot Springs Country Club, 107
        - Napa - Silverado, 108
        - Newhall Ranch, 433
        - Newport Beach, 434
        - Oxnard - Cape Malibu, 109
        - Palm Canyon, 120
        - Palm Springs - Hidden Valley, 117
        - Palm Springs Mobile, 118
        - Palo Alto - Stanford University Golf Course, 125, 436
        - Palos Verdes - Palos Verdes Development, 120
        - Pebble Beach - Cypress Point Golf Course, 109
        - Pebble Beach - Spyglass Hill Golf Club, 121
        - Rancho - Rancho California Country Club, 122
        - Roxborough Park, 118
        - Sacramento - El Dorado Hills West, 112, 113, 114, 115
        - Sam Snead, 123, 124
        - San Diego - Tecolote Canyon, 126
        - San Francisco - Olympic Country Club, 109
        - San Leandro, 433
        - Santa Barbara - Birnam Wood Golf Club, 106, 434
        - Ventura Co., 127
        - Weed - Lake Shastina, 118
        - Wilson, 433
        - Woodside - Woodside Golf Course, 127
      - Colorado
        - Aspen - Aspen-Wildcat, 121
        - Avon - Beaver Creek Golf Course, 430
        - Boulder City - Boulder City Golf Course, 110
        - Colorado Springs - Broadmoor Golf Club, 128, 129, 470
        - Colorado Springs - Garden of the Gods, 110
        - Colorado Springs - US Air Force Academy, 133
        - Denver - Cherry Hills Country Club, 121
        - Denver - Ken Caryl Ranch, 107, 130, 131
        - Denver - Lonetree, 132
        - Denver - Ruby Hills Country Club, 132
        - Steamboat Springs - Steamboat Springs Golf Course, 132
        - Union County - Galloping Hills Park Golf Course, 130
        - Vail - Vail Project, 133
        - River Ranch, 436
        - Telluride, 133
      - Connecticut
        - Ashford - Royal Oaks, 139
        - Candlewood Park, 134
        - Danbury - Ridgewood Country Club, 142, 143
        - Durham, 127
        - E. Haddam - Old Lyme, 140
        - Essex - Connecticut Valley Country Club, 135
        - Fairfield - Country Club of Fairfield, 135
        - Fairfield - Patterson Club, 141
        - Greenwich - Fairview Country Club, 136
        - Greenwich - Greenwich Country Club, 136, 436
        - Greenwich - Greenwich Municipal Golf Course, 135
        - Hamden - Hamden Golf Course, 137
        - Middlebury - Whittmore Property, 143
        - Middlefield - Lyman Meadows Golf Course, 139
        - New Canaan - Country Club of New Canaan, 135
        - Old Greenwich - Innis Arden, 138
        - Old Lyme - Black Hall Club, 134
        - Orange - Race Brook Country Club, 142
        - Pine Orchard - Pine Orchard Club, 141
        - Pittsfield, 141
        - Stamford - Rock Rimmon Country Club, 142
        - Stanford Bello, 136
        - Tumblebrook C.C., 143
        - Wallingford - Pilgrims Harbor, 141
        - West Hartford - Hartford Golf Club, 137, 138
        - West Minnich-Ridgefield - The Carriages, 143
        - Westport - Westport Estates, Inc., 143
        - Wilton - Langner Property, 138
      - Delaware
        - Seaford - Seaford Golf and Country Club, 144
        - Wilmington - Wilmington Country Club, 144, 145, 436
      - Florida
        - 1000 Acre housing, 440
        - Augustine, 348
        - Biltmore, Coral Gables, 155
        - Boca Raton - Boca Raton Golf & Country Club, 149
        - Boca Raton - Royal Palm Yacht & C.C., 183
        - Broward Co. - Davie Prop., 161, 162
        - Broward Co. - Hillsboro, 118
        - Broward County - Three Islands, 186
        - Cocoa Beach - Patrick Air Force Base, 180
        - Coral Springs, 155
        - Cranberry Meadow, 438
        - Crandon Park, 160
        - Del Ray Beach - Pine Tree, 438
        - Delray Beach - Kings Point Golf Course, 171
        - Fort Lauderdale - American Golfers Club, 146. 147
        - Fort Lauderdale - Coral Ridge Country Club, 147, 152, 153, 154, 155, 156, 157, 158, 179
        - Fort Lauderdale - Dania - Cut off Canal, 150
        - Golden Ocala, 160, 437
        - Grande Point, 439
        - Haines City - Arrowhead Golf & Country Club, 149
        - Haulover Beach - Sam Snead Par-3, 123, 124
        - Hialeah - Country Club of Miami, 159
        - Hobe Sound, 140
        - Hollywood - Golden Isles, 150
        - Interama, 168
        - Jacksonville - Belle Terre Country Club, 150
        - Jacksonville Beach - Jacksonville Beach Municipal Golf Course, 150
        - Key Biscayne, 439, 458
        - Lauderhill - Inverrary Golf and Country Club, 169, 170
        - Longboat Key, 173
        - Manatee County, 359
        - Martin Co. - Rossmoor-Stuart (lead), 183
        - Martin Co. - Summerfield, 450
        - Mathews Grove, LTD, 174
        - Melbourne - Suntree Golf Course, 185
        - Miami - MacDonald Property, 174
        - Miami - West Miami Planning, 437
        - Miami - Jejeune Golf Club, 172
        - Naples - Flamingo Island Club (Lely prop), 163, 164, 165
        - Naples - Lely G.C., 173
        - North Golden Gate, 162
        - Orlando - Birdmen's Inn and C.C., 150
        - Orlando - Celebration GC (Disney), 151
        - Orlando - Hyatt House Resort, 168
        - Orlando - Lakewood C.C., 171
        - Orlando - Metrowest, 175, 176
        - Orlando - Orlando Country Club, 177
        - Palm Beach - La Coquille Golf Club, 171
        - Palm Beach - Seminole Beach Development, 184
        - Palm Coast - Palm Coast, 178
        - PGA, 438
        - Polk Co. - River Ranch East, 101
        - Pompano Beach C.C., 180
        - Ponte Vedra Beach - Ponte Vedra Club, 181, 183
        - Port Charlotte - Porzio Property, 182
        - Riegel Paper Co., 441
        - Sarasota - Grenada Golf Course, 437
        - So. Desseret Lake - Deseret, 161
        - Southern Woods, 437
        - St. Augustine - St. John Co., 107
        - Stuart - Seabranch G. C., 184
        - Tallahassee - Tallahassee, 185
        - Tampa - Apollo Beach Country Club, 418
        - Tampa - Cypress Lakes, 160
        - Tampa - Tampa, 185
        - Tarpon Springs - Fox Hollow, 166, 167
        - Titusville, 437
        - Titusville - All American Golf Course, 146
      - Georgia
        - Albany - The Oaks, 195
        - Alpharetta - Windward Properties, 195
        - Athens - University of Georgia Golf Course, 195, 196, 441
        - Atlanta - Capital City Golf Club, 133
        - Atlanta - Holder (Robert) Property, 191
        - Atlanta - Peachtree Golf Course, 192, 193, 441, 450
        - Atlanta - Standard Town & Country Club, 194
        - Augusta - Augusta National Golf Club, 187, 441
        - Augusta - Gordon Lakes Golf Club, 190
        - Carrollton - Carrollton Golf Club, 188
        - Decatur - Fairington Golf and Tennis Club, 189
        - Druid Hills, 183
        - Duluth - Atlanta Athletic Club, 187
        - Fort Benning - Fort Benning Golf Course, 190
        - Fulton Co. - Rivermont, 191
        - Gainesville - Gainesville Municipal Golf Course, 190, 467
        - Sapeloe Island - Sapeloe Island Golf Club, 191, 194
        - Savannah - Savannah G.C., 223
        - Sea Island - Sea Island Golf Club, 194
        - Stone Mountain - Stone Mountain Golf Course, 188, 194
        - Thomaston - Thomaston Country Club, 194
      - Hawaii
        - Honolulu - Hawaii Kai, 197
        - Honolulu - Moanalua Golf Club, 207
        - Kaanapali, 198, 442, 448, 450
        - Kamuela - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel Golf Course, 204, 205, 206, 450
        - Kauai - Princeville Golf Club, 203
        - Kaunaoa Beach, 199, 200, 201, 202, 442
        - Lihi Lani, 450
        - Maui - Kaupulehu, 102
        - Maui - Makena Golf Course, 203
        - Maui - Wailea Golf Course, 143
        - Mauna Kea - Queen's Land, 208, 209, 450
        - Mauna Kea - Rockefeller Waimea Property, 209
        - Waikoloa - Waikoloa Village Colf Course, 209
      - Idaho
        - Sun Valley - Elkhorn Golf Club, 210
        - Village Course Boise Cascade, 209
      - Illinois
        - Carbondale - Southern Illinois University, 216
        - Chicago - Old Elm Club, 216
        - Chicago - Worth Project, 219
        - Fox River Grove, 212
        - Highland Park, 443
        - Highland Park - Exmoor Club, 211
        - Hilldale - Hilldale Golf Course, 211, 213
        - Lake Forest - Knollwood Club, 214
        - Lake Forest - Lake Forest, 214, 215, 442
        - Lincolnshire - Marriott Project, 216
        - Springfield - Rail, The, 218
        - St. Charles - Pottawatomie Park Golf Club, 217
      - Indiana
        - Bloomington - Indiana University, 220
        - Columbus - Cummins Engine Golf Course, 217
        - Columbus - Otter Creek Golf Club, 220, 221, 442
        - Santa Claus Land, 220
      - Kansas
        - Charolaise G.C., 222
        - Johnson Co. - Quail Valley (Alternate Site), 223
        - Wichita - Crestview country Club, 118, 222
      - Kentucky
        - Apple Valley, 121
        - Frankfort, 224
        - Lexington - Higbee Mills (Bellamy), 224
        - Louisville - Executive Country Club, 125
        - Paducah - Paducah, Country Club of, 224
        - Somerset - Woodson Bend (lead), 225
      - Louisiana
        - Baton Rouge - Santa Maria Golf Club, 226
        - Covington - Covington C.C., 24
        - Gretna - Timberlane Country Club, 227, 463
        - New Orleans - New Orleans C.C., 137
      - Maine
        - Adams - Mount Greylock, 186
        - East Stoneham - Evergreen Valley Golf Course, 246, 445
        - Portland - Portland Country Club, 137
        - Yarmouth - Yarmouth Properties, 247
        - York - Mt. Agamentieus, 245, 470
      - Maryland
        - Annapolis - Annapolis Yacht & Country Club, 237
        - Anne Arundel Co. - Golden Triangle, 242, 247
        - Baltimore - Elkridge Club, 241
        - Baltimore - Kingswood Yacht & Country Club, 237
        - Baltimore - Suburban Country Club, 245
        - Baltimore Co. - Mc Kenzie, 237
        - Baltimore Co. - The Glenn L. Martin Company, 195
        - Baltimore County - Worthington Valley C.C., 195, 257
        - Bethesda - Burning Tree Golf Course, 237
        - Bethesda - Congressional C. C., 240
        - Cecil County plans, 257
        - Championship Golf Course, 452
        - Chestertown - Great Oak Lodge, 237
        - Chevy Chase - Colombia Country Club, 237
        - Dupont, 241, 444
        - Emmitsburg (lead), 241
        - Garrison - Green Spring Valley Hunt Club, 237
        - Hagerstown - Hagerstown G. C., 243
        - Hexton Farms, 445
        - Hunt Valley - R P Farms, 237
        - Ocean City - Dorment Prop. (lead), 229
        - Ocean City - Ocean Pines Country Club (Seabright), 244, 444
        - Patuxent - Cedar Point Golf Club Naval Air Station, 237
        - Prince George County - Belmont, 102
        - Riger Property, 244
        - River Oaks Farm, 180
      - Massachusetts
        - Adams - Greylock Glen, 230
        - Bernardston - Crumpin-Fox Club, 238
        - Beverly - The Montserrat G.C., 233
        - Bolton - International Golf Course, 229
        - Eastham, 121
        - Fall River - Fall River Properties, 228
        - Falmouth, 228
        - Franklin C.C., 229
        - Gloucester, 229, 230
        - Haverhill - Haverhill Golf & Country Club, 228
        - Ipswich - Ipswich Country Club, 230, 231
        - Mashpee, Cape Cod - Whitcomb Landing, 235
        - Milton, 232
        - MIT, 443
        - N. Dartmouth - Hawthorne Country Club, 228
        - Osterville - Oyster Harbors Country Club, 137
        - Peabody - Salem Country Club, 233
        - Plymouth - White Cliffs of Plymouth, 236
        - S. Dartmouth - Round Hill, 232
        - Taunton - Chick Gelich Prop., 228
        - Topsfield C.C., 234
        - Wellesley - Wellesley Country Club, 235
        - Wianno C.C., 236
        - Woodland C.C., 35, 237
      - Michigan
        - Benton Harbor - Point O'Woods Golf Course, 253, 254, 465
        - Birmingham - Birmingham Country Club, 248
        - Birmingham - C. J. Snyder Golf Club, 174
        - Birmingham - Oakland Hills Country Club, 252, 447
        - Bloomfield Hills - Bloomfield Hills Country Club, 250
        - Bloomfield Hills - Fox Run, 182
        - Detroit - Knollwood Country Club, 214
        - E. Lansing - Michigan State University Forest Akers, 251
        - Gaylord - Treetops at Sylvan Resort, 255, 256, 243
        - Grand Rapids - Kirchgessner Property, 448
        - Grosse Point Farms - Detroit, Country Club of, 251
        - Harbor Springs - Boyne Highlands, 249, 259
        - Jackson - R. W. Hancock Golf Club, 174
        - Lansing - Black Project, 249
        - Oakland County - Sylvan Glen, 254
        - Rochester - Rochester Country Club, 253
        - Royal Oak - Red Run Golf Club, 174
        - Grand Rapids, 130
        - Oxford, 253
        - Tam O'Shanter, 236
        - The Settlement, 446, 447
        - Traverse City, 180
        - Wabeek Farms, 256
      - Minnesota
        - Chaska - Hazeltine National Golf Club, 256
        - Elkhorn Golf Club, 375
        - Madden Inn, 119
        - Minneapolis - Interlachen Country Club, 257
        - Sunfish Lake, 257
      - Mississippi
        - Scott Co. - Roosevelt State Park, 266
      - Missouri
        - Clayton - St. Louis Country Club, 265
        - Creve Coeur - Bellerive Country Club, 258, 259, 445
        - Eureka - Legends, Country Club as the, 261, 262, 263
        - Eureka - Winding Brook Country Club, 265
        - Franklin County - Franklin County C.C., 259
        - Kansas City - Armendaris Dev. (lead), 225
        - Kansas City - Blue Hills Country Club, 147
        - Jackson County, 241
        - LaDue - Old Warson Country Club, 264
        - Lake of the Ozarks - Four Seasons Golf and Country Club, 260
        - Sedalia - Westmoreland Country Club, 265
        - St. Charles Co. - Lake St. Louis (lead), 261
        - St. Louis - Wolfner Property, 266
      - Montana
        - Billings - 3 Wolf Ranch, 266
        - Billings - Yellowstone Country Club, 108, 267, 469
      - Nebraska
        - Lincoln - Devils Nest Development Corp., 279
        - Omaha - Offutt Air Force Base, 280
        - Omaha - Omaha Country Club, 174, 279
      - Nevada
        - Lake Tahoe - Incline Village Golf Course, 247
        - Reno - Jackzig, 108
        - Southern Highlands, 464
      - New Hampshire
        - Antrim - Doleac, 281
        - Derry, 118
        - Farmington - Am-Tec, 281
        - Keene - Keene Country Club, 228
        - Lake Tarleton, 281
        - Portsmouth - Pease Air Force Base, 142
        - Portsmouth - Portsmouth Country Club, 282
        - Windham - Windham C.C. (Ruggiero Prop), 248
      - New Jersey
        - Allamuchy - Panther Valley, 302, 453
        - Atlantic City - (lead 1988), 102
        - Atlantic City - Galloway Township, 186
        - Atlantic City - Greenberg Prop., 219
        - Atlantic Co. - Reeds Bay, 135
        - Basking Ridge - Sutton Construction, 294
        - Bedminster - Johns Manville Prop, 296
        - Cacapon State Park, 285
        - Clementon - Pine Valley Golf Club, 261, 304
        - Clifton - Upper Montclair Country Club, 307, 413
        - Colts Neck - Colts Neck (Armand Hammer), 149
        - Colts Neck - Hominy Hill Golf Course, 293, 294, 453
        - Convent Sta. - Morris County G.C., 294
        - Cranbury Township - Cranbury Township, 287
        - Creskill Hills, 288
        - Cresskill - Tammy Brook Country Club, 306
        - Deal - Deal Golf & Country Club, 287
        - Demarest - Alpine C.C., 282
        - Eatontown - Picola Property, 289
        - Essex Fells - Essex Fells Country Club, 289, 191
        - Flanders - Peacock Farms, 303
        - Glen Ridge - Glen Ridge Country Club, 291
        - Glouster Co., 230
        - Great Swamp, 292
        - Hackensack - Meadowlands, 299
        - Haddonfield - Tavistock Country Club, 306
        - Hanover - New Egypt, 289
        - Haworth, 136
        - High Hills, 453
        - Holmdel - Holmdel, Makena, 168, 295
        - Hopewell - Hopewell Valley, 294
        - Jackson Township - Metedeconk National Golf Club, 301
        - Jersey City - Liberty State Park, 298
        - Lake Mohawk - Arthur D. Crane Co., 283
        - Lakehurst, 452
        - Lawrenceville - Green Acres Country Club, 118
        - Liberty Corner - USGA Golf Course, 307
        - Liberty Corners - USGA Site, 294
        - Livingston - Cedar Hill, 285
        - Livingston - Cedar Hills, 286
        - Lyons - Veterans Administration Hospital, 291
        - Mahwah, 298
        - Manasquan, 15
        - McAfee - Great Gorge Village G.C., 292
        - Medford Lakes - Medford Lakes Country Club, 289
        - Mendham - Mendham Golf & C.C., 300
        - Middletown - Iler, 133
        - Middletown Township - Everett Estates, 289
        - Monmouth Co./Holmdel Twsp. - Marlu Farms, 299
        - Montclair - Montclair Golf Club, 254, 300, 303
        - Montgomery Twsp. - Princeton Lead, 304
        - Morris Co. - Fleming-Stone Project, 120
        - Morris Plains - Craftsman Farms, 138
        - Morris Plains - Farney Property, 289
        - Musconetcong - Musconetcong Country Club, 289
        - Newton - Newton Country Club, 289
        - No. Caldwell - Green Brook Country Club, 261